tassimodirect.com 2016-11-27

# Gevalia Coffee Privacy Policy

##### Effective Date:1/15/2015

The Gevalia website is operated by Kraft New Services, Inc., a subsidiary of Kraft Foods Group. We recognize that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us and how we handle that information.

  * Information We Collect
  * Personally-Identifiable Information
  * Registration
  * Contests, Sweepstakes and Games
  * E-mail
  * Community
  * "Contact Us" Link
  * Shopping
  * Refer A Friend / Send To A Friend
  * Other Site Features
  * Questionnaires and Surveys
  * Information Collected By Automated Means
  * Information We Collect From Other Sources
  * How We Use Your Information
  * Links To Other Websites
  * Your Choices
  * Children's Information
  * How We Protect Your Information
  * Updates To This Privacy Notice
  * How to Contact Us

#####   

#### Types Of Information We Collect

#####   

##### Personally-Identifiable Information

On our website, we collect certain personally-identifiable information, such as name, telephone number, e-mail address and, if you’re a Gevalia customer, payment information, about online visitors who choose to register on our website or participate in our offers and programs. We don’t require you to register or provide personally-identifiable information to view our site or access much of its content. But if you register, you may use certain additional features and participate in our interactive communities. Sharing this additional information with us also helps us customize your website experience. In addition, we may use the information you provide us to send you offers and information about Gevalia, Kraft and its portfolio of brands, and our partners. Here are the ways we collect personally-identifiable information.  
Back To Top

##### Registration

To take full advantage of our offers, you may choose to register on our site. In the registration process, we may request certain information (such as your contact information and age) so we can provide you with the communications and products you request, tailor our website to better meet your needs, and customize our contacts with you.  
Back To Top

##### Contests, Sweepstakes and Games

We may provide contests, sweepstakes and games that you can enter. We use the information you provide to conduct the promotion (for example, to contact you if you’re a winner) and to provide you with offers and information as described in this privacy notice.  
Back To Top

##### E-mail

When you ask us to send you newsletters, information, or other content by e-mail, you may provide us with certain information like your e-mail address so we can fulfill your request.  
Back To Top

##### Community

When you participate through the Community portion of our site, such as submitting a review, using our message boards, or other interactive functions, you may submit information and content, such as a rating, picture, geographic location, etc. to the site. Remember that what you post or upload to the site will be publicly available, so please exercise caution when deciding whether to disclose anything personal about yourself. Gevalia cannot control the actions of third parties who may view the website and use publicly-available information for their own purposes.  
Back To Top

##### "Contact Us" Link

If you contact us through the "Contact Us" link on this site or via telephone, we ask you for information such as your first name, e-mail address, and other information, so we can respond to your questions and comments. You may choose to provide additional information as well.  
Back To Top

##### Shopping

When you purchase products or services from Gevalia, we request your billing information so we can fulfill your request. We use your billing information to fulfill your order and provide complimentary samples.  
Back To Top

##### Refer A Friend / Send To A Friend

We may give you the opportunity to tell your friends about features or information on our website. If you take advantage of our Refer a Friend / Send to a Friend option, we ask you for your friend’s and your first name and e-mail addresses to send the information to them that you requested. We may keep this information to identify when your friend makes a purchase so we can provide you with the appropriate rewards.  
Back To Top

##### Other Site Features

We offer visitors to our website various features for their enjoyment, which we change from time to time. We may ask you to submit certain personally-identifiable information so we can provide you with these features.  
Back To Top

##### Questionnaires and Surveys

We may ask our website visitors and purchasers to complete surveys and opinion polls to provide feedback on activities, attitudes and interests. These surveys help us understand the needs of our visitors and purchasers.  
Back To Top

##### Information Collected By Automated Means

We may use cookies, web beacons/pixel tags, log files, and other technologies to collect certain information about visitors to our website, use of our online services, and interactions with our emails and online advertisements. For example, through these means, we may collect your browser type and operating system, viewed webpages, links that are clicked, IP address, sites visited before coming to our website, emails we send that you open, forward, or click through to our website. Collecting this information, and linking it with your personally-identifiable information, helps us to best tailor our website and enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site, and to help identify site features, advertisements, and offers that may be of particular interest to you.

We also may use third party advertisements placed by ad networks to support our site. Some of these advertisers and ad networks may use technology such as cookies and web beacons/pixel tags when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers and ad networks information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and whether you have Flash installed. Some of these advertisers and ad networks also may use anonymous data, such as demographic data, received from third parties to assist in the delivery of advertisements to you. These advertisers and ad networks use the information described above to provide you relevant advertisements based on your online behavior, search activities on our site and on other third party sites, demographic information and/or relevant to your general location, so that the advertising you see on our site more closely reflects your interests and needs. For example, if you search for, or browse a, recipe or product on our site, you may see an advertisement from a third party with information about, or an offer similar to, that for which you were searching or browsing on our site, or an offer related to a third party whose site you have visited in the past. We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising.

You can set your Internet browser settings to stop accepting new cookies, to receive notice when you receive a new cookie, to disable existing cookies, to omit images (which will disable pixel tags), and adjust your tracking preferences. Note that the opt-out will apply only to the browser that you are using when you elect to opt out of advertising cookies. Note, however, that our systems may not recognize Do Not Track (DNT) headers from some or all browsers. You can learn more about and opt out from receiving third party advertiser cookies by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). Without cookies or pixel tags though, you may not be able to take full advantage of all the website features.  
Back To Top

##### Information We Collect From Other Sources

We may obtain information about you from other sources, including commercially available sources, such as data aggregators and public databases. This information may include name, demographic information, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media and shopping behavior. We may combine this information with the information we collect from you to help us tailor our communications to you and to improve our services and products.  
Back To Top

##### How We Use Your Information

We may use the information we collect to contact you from time to time. For example, we may (i) send you promotional offers, materials, and other communications and information about Gevalia, Kraft and its portfolio of brands, and our partners, (ii) respond to your comments or questions, or (iii) contact you if needed while processing a product or service you requested through our website. We also may use the information you provide to contact you for your opinions on our products, services or websites. As described in this Privacy Notice, we also use the information we collect about you to improve our website, products and services, and to deliver content that is customized to your interests.  
Back To Top

##### How We Share Your Information

We do not sell or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information about our website visitors, except as described here. We do not share your personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties for their own marketing purposes without your consent. For California residents, please see “Your California Privacy Rights” below.

We may share personally identifiable information with our parent company, Kraft, including its brands and subsidiaries. We may also share the information with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf, such as to help run promotions, fulfill orders and provide customer service. These service providers may have access to personally-identifiable information about our website visitors if it is needed to perform their functions for us, but they are not authorized to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. In addition, we may disclose information where we think it’s necessary to investigate or prevent an actual or suspected crime or injury to ourselves or others, if required by law, or in response to a request from law enforcement authorities or other government officials.

We may conduct joint promotions with other companies. We may share with our promotional partners (and their service providers) certain personally-identifiable information as necessary to conduct the promotion. We will not share this information with our promotional partners for any other purpose unless you consent to such sharing.

During the normal course of our business, we may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personally identifiable information provided through this website in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice.  
Back To Top

##### Your California Privacy Rights

For California Residents: We may share your personally-identifiable information with affiliated third parties, some of which do not share the Gevalia or Kraft name, for their own direct marketing purposes. Because this category of affiliates is considered to be “unaffiliated parties” under California Law, you may opt out of us sharing with them. To opt out, please send a letter with your name, postal address, e-mail, with the heading “California Privacy Rights” to:

Gevalia Kaffe

Attention: Customer Service

1201 Elm Street, 4th Floor Dallas, TX 75270  
Back To Top

##### Links to Other Websites

This website may contain links to other websites. We provide these links solely for your convenience and information. Different websites have different privacy practices. You should always check the privacy notice of the specific site you’re visiting to understand the privacy practices associated with that site. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of third party websites.  
Back To Top

##### 

##### Your Choices

You can change your preferences for follow-up contacts by us. If you’re registered with our website, you can change the information you’ve provided to us in the "My Profile" section of the site.

If you wish to limit how third parties use your email address to send you targeted advertising through social media on our behalf, contact us [here](http://www.kraftrecipes.com/registration/useroptout.aspx). Please allow 10 days for your email to be removed from our marketing database.  
Back To Top

##### 

##### Children's Information

This site is intended for general audiences and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13.  
Back To Top

##### 

##### How We Protect Your Information

The security of personally-identifiable information is important to us. We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized use, disclosure, alteration or destruction of the personally-identifiable information we collect on this website.  
Back To Top

##### 

##### Updates To This Privacy Notice

We may change or update portions of this Privacy Notice at any time. Please check back from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates to the notice. We will indicate the notice’s effective date on the first page of the notice.  
Back To Top

##### How To Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice, you can contact us at:

Gevalia Kaffe

Attn: Customer Service

Elm Street, 4th Floor Dallas, TX 75270

1-800-GEVALIA (1-800-438-2542)

8 AM – 8 PM EST Monday through Friday.

We would be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns.  
Back To Top
